Is crash Bandicoot worked a deep and emotional experience that will last with you a lifetime
[or] is it Satan's way of turning children into Vegans well this review will talk about neither of those things
In two weeks, I will have a new garbage review out
But now I wanted to try something new something no one has ever done before something revolutionary. [I] want to review an
Older game [crash] Bandicoot was made by naughty dog when they were still [in] their prime today
They have completely lost it
You are insane if you think this is a good platformer work start right after the second game with the [space] [place]
Crashing into this prison [that] is housing booga ooga
And evil [mask] [then] we see our classic villain Cortex talking to Coca who is his boss apparently? He's like
I'm sorry crash took me those two times and
Honestly if I was so coca right now I wouldn't even be [Madeleine] even care about that because the odds of a space station
crashing into your prison are
Astronomical so I would be like hoardings. Fuck that okay listen go to the supermarket
Lottery tickets all of them disappointingly. He's more like [ya] Cortex crash
He stole all our crystals, but we still don't take over the world, but we need the crystals to take over the world
How are no corvettes?
Well are we cuckoo Cos hire this guy to build a time machine
So I guess maybe he didn't actually need lottery money anyways. I mean look at this place Musta cost at least six seven
Thousand dollars. I don't know what the time machine cost, but in Middle school
We put up a musical version of Schindler's list and those kinds of backdrops costs a fortune
Lucky for us crash gets there first and now he's going to [jump] to different places in time to get the crystals
We have [five] different worlds to unlock medieval Europe Disney's aladdin
China ancient egypt, and of course Finland, how do I know that's finland in our hearts
Don't we all everyone has five levels do they have something to do with the actual world no
Usually one [of] the levels is kind of relevant has the same theme well except for the [shinies] one
Doesn't have a shiniest level even though they are extremely fun
But they make up for [that] by having the egyptian world have two egyptian levels even though they are super
Mediocre so you get the crystal from the [higher] levels then there's a boss [after] [you] beat the boss
You unlock the next world where you find five new levels some of them have the same thing as the last levels
Except for a new element like nighttime but some levels have a completely new theme for [example] in the second world
There's a level set in America
[as] it happens the levels set in United States are also the worst in the game does that make crash
Bandicoot anti-America
I think the evidence speaks for itself also when you beat a boss you get [a] special ability [for] example first boss
You get the [body's] [flammability]?
[and] [then] the double jump then the super Spin and when you beat the [fourth] boss you get a bazooka
Well that took a somewhat interesting turn off to beat the last boss. They will be all like hey. It's not over yet
We still got the great crystals, so that's nice. I guess but the truth is it was a really bad [idea] from the start
[Kukuku] Listen start smaller first take over like a local government see if you like it
Enjoy it
see if it fits you then maybe move on now go a little bigger because you don't want to be there in five years and
Have taken over the entire planet, and then you're like well
This is not what [I] wanted and I'm not enjoying this at all. I would have made an excellent
Music teacher also when you beat last boss
You unlock the last ability speed shoes they help when you are attempting to get the relics. Which is a Sorta
Speedrunning reward for every five relic you get you get a new map in the underground America world
There are three types of relics sapphire gold and platinum [you] only need this Fi one to unlock the new world
But if you only get sapphire you should turn off your playstation and throw it away as you are casual scum
I think that the game's biggest problem
Is that it [doesn't] have online matchmaking now you might be saying well the first playstation didn't have online capabilities
But that's no excuse though is it because I've still developed online matchmaking
[it's] just pure laziness from the developers also the second problem. Is [that] the Nostalgia from this game is killing me on the inside
No, dog should have made way worse. [so] I didn't take it as much as a kid this game is great
And I really love it actually [this] game is shaped fuck this to class game
Well other than the game being complete shit. [I] kind of like this game if you're interested in crash Bandicoot worked
You should probably check out another review, and that's the kilian experience liked it. You liked it in two weeks
I will have a new garbage review out an actual real one. I mean this was a bit different with retro thing
I'm leaning towards the first assassin's creed, but I could also do Dragon age origins
But you know what you can request if you want to cast any any game you want
Comment comment what you want to see?